/**
 * Product Database can be added here.
 * You can add products of your wish with different attributes
 * */

export const quizzes = [
  {
    _id: "094454fe-ff7c-4a13-9adb-06801f9e379a",
    title: "A-Z Birds",
    totalScore: 10,
    mcqs: [
      {
        _id: "fd5f7ecc-8ac2-4cbf-b474-fae6f9abc544",
        question:
          "_________ is an exceedingly large seabird, having a wingspan as much as 11 feet across",
        options: ["Albatross", "Dove", "Razorbill", "Puffin"],
        answer: "Albatross",
      },
      {
        _id: "3f950919-15b0-4b8e-abf1-bb375b690f9b",
        question: "The pigment in Blue Jay feather is of which color?",
        options: ["Blue", "Brown", "White", "Red"],
        answer: "Brown",
      },
      {
        _id: "48e34d4a-032d-4ab3-b989-2f4d43495df6",
        question:
          "_________ are non-migratory birds as they prefer to live within a mile of where they were born.",
        options: ["Razorbill", "Albatross", "Cardinal", "Crane"],
        answer: "Cardinal",
      },
      {
        _id: "575b11fc-2234-4cb4-b9a4-b9089e769e5e",
        question: "_________ is a symbol of peace.",
        options: ["Razorbill", "Albatross", "Cardinal", "Dove"],
        answer: "Dove",
      },
      {
        _id: "83037a69-4a98-47f0-9aaf-c13b707a470b",
        question: "A group of Eagles is called a _________",
        options: ["convocation", "eaglets", "flock", "swarm"],
        answer: "convocation",
      },
      {
        _id: "96b87fc4-1cd9-4800-89d6-14516d942568",
        question: "A group of crows is called a _________",
        options: ["convocation", "murder", "flock", "swarm"],
        answer: "murder",
      },
      {
        _id: "15c97172-d081-459e-b6cf-27ac94b2c48c",
        question:
          "_________ can identify food that it finds while probing with its beak without seeing it first, thanks to sensitive feelers inside its bill",
        options: ["Albatross", "Kingfisher", "Ibis", "Puffin"],
        answer: "Ibis",
      },
      {
        _id: "4ba721e7-d554-4dfb-9bce-8db72b6fa342",
        question: "_________ often appear to be walking on the water itself",
        options: ["Kingfisher", "Ibis", "Flamingo", "Jacana"],
        answer: "Jacana",
      },
      {
        _id: "b41f2993-b7ec-447a-904f-6ab9c9c64592",
        question:
          "_________ can sing over 200 songs, including those of other birds, insect, amphibians, and even mechanical sounds.",
        options: ["Mockingbird", "Cuckoo", "Myna", "Starling"],
        answer: "Mockingbird",
      },
      {
        _id: "2935d37b-20b7-40ce-a3e5-8c64c82aad96",
        question: "Which Bird Is the Fastest Runner?",
        options: ["Roadrunner", "Emu", "Ostrich", "Cassowary"],
        answer: "Ostrich",
      },
    ],
    categoryId: "stvcat001",
    categoryName: "Bird Quiz",
  },
  {
    _id: "5094b503-d0f1-490d-888c-117ae7aa5f59",
    title: "Heavy Weight",
    totalScore: 10,
    mcqs: [
      {
        _id: "43bc8711-250a-415f-a162-aabbfa4072fb",
        question: "Which bird falls under this weight category: 24 to 35 lb",
        options: ["Bustard", "Stork", "Sea Eagle", "Pelican"],
        answer: "Bustard",
      },
      {
        _id: "c52d1120-5cf8-4a4e-afd5-a5fcb8a8a979",
        question: "Which bird falls under this weight category: 26 to 33 lb",
        options: ["Stork", "Swan", "Sea Eagle", "Pelican"],
        answer: "Swan",
      },
      {
        _id: "9ae23884-1b86-4715-9bab-9f8b5ebdce97",
        question: "Which bird falls under this weight category: 24 to 33 lb",
        options: ["Stork", "Pelican", "Condor", "Sea Eagle"],
        answer: "Condor",
      },
      {
        _id: "72c2adab-381d-444b-8f35-5fde72f92118",
        question: "Which bird falls under this weight category: 15 to 31 lb",
        options: ["Finch", "Kingfisher", "Flycatcher", "Vulture"],
        answer: "Vulture",
      },
      {
        _id: "2e494b62-75b7-49ac-9897-dc493e3beacc",
        question: "Which bird falls under this weight category: 14 to 26 lb",
        options: ["Albatross", "Woodpecker", "Mockingbird", "Swan"],
        answer: "Albatross",
      },
      {
        _id: "0d1434df-6f78-474e-9538-8e60a43486e4",
        question: "Which bird falls under this weight category: 11 to 26 lb",
        options: ["Swan", "Crane", "Finch", "Sparrow"],
        answer: "Crane",
      },
      {
        _id: "ef5d937d-1e32-4ee2-82e7-5a6621b1d1cc",
        question: "Which bird falls under this weight category: 11 to 24 lb",
        options: ["Bustard", "Swan", "Wild Turkey", "Condor"],
        answer: "Wild Turkey",
      },
      {
        _id: "96296f88-12e3-4954-b4f5-4de651a03d27",
        question: "Which bird falls under this weight category: 10 to 22 lb",
        options: ["Bustard", "Swan", "Condor", "Pelican"],
        answer: "Pelican",
      },
      {
        _id: "07b27c13-c511-40d1-9f26-3441f0e8568e",
        question: "Which bird falls under this weight category: 11 to 20 lb",
        options: ["Sea Eagle", "Bustard", "Swan", "Condor"],
        answer: "Sea Eagle",
      },
      {
        _id: "d1457c29-23d2-4802-955e-b78b85191877",
        question: "Which bird falls under this weight category: 10 to 18 lb",
        options: ["Bustard", "Swan", "Stork", "Condor"],
        answer: "Stork",
      },
    ],
    categoryId: "stvcat001",
    categoryName: "Bird Quiz",
  },
  {
    _id: "806f82bf-7038-4580-adab-547e06fef18a",
    title: "Fictional Birds",
    totalScore: 10,
    mcqs: [
      {
        _id: "7848b9ce-fd1d-4966-982a-82838f24c000",
        question: "He typically wears a sailor shirt and cap with a bow tie.",
        options: [
          "Donald Duck",
          "Count Duckula",
          "Baby Huey",
          "Scrooge McDuck",
        ],
        answer: "Donald Duck",
      },
      {
        _id: "ac5721cb-a38c-438f-92a6-5cb9455f949a",
        question:
          "His family is very poor, so he emigrates to USA where he finds gold and becomes rich.",
        options: [
          "Donald Duck",
          "Scrooge McDuck",
          "Chilly Willy",
          "Plucky Duck",
        ],
        answer: "Scrooge McDuck",
      },
      {
        _id: "689b5a36-7d06-4192-9c86-ae7cd2341a7e",
        question: "_________ became the mascot for Froot Loops cereal in 1963.",
        options: ["Scuttle", "Tweety Bird", "Toucan Sam", "Donald Duck"],
        answer: "Toucan Sam",
      },
      {
        _id: "dd0f1b77-931a-41e6-8faa-9e4c7cba4865",
        question:
          "_________ appears in Walt Disney Pictures' 31st animated feature film Aladdin",
        options: ["Zazu", "Beaky Buzzard", "Henery Hawk", "Iago"],
        answer: "Iago",
      },
      {
        _id: "97bb5615-a03f-4a2e-9faf-b5ac8687fb29",
        question:
          "_________ is a tiny, brown chicken hawk with a forelock of feathers. The young bird lives at home with his parents, and speaks with tough-guy bravado.",
        options: ["Henery Hawk", "Beaky Buzzard", "Toucan Sam", "Scuttle"],
        answer: "Henery Hawk",
      },
      {
        _id: "55d1cd8a-c00a-4ec4-91c4-515efa051553",
        question:
          "The most famous bird in the iconic Lion King film is _________, a red-billed hornbill who plays the flying wise mentor to Mufasa and later Simba.",
        options: ["Scuttle", "Zazu", "Toucan Sam", "Iago"],
        answer: "Zazu",
      },
      {
        _id: "85bd9c0f-1c15-4f9b-99c2-489a66ed2723",
        question:
          "_________ was also the first Disney animated show to be a straight-up parody and send up elements of other media and popular culture.",
        options: ["Daisy Duck", "Donald Duck", "Darkwing Duck", "Plucky Duck"],
        answer: "Darkwing Duck",
      },
      {
        _id: "48285c75-e582-45ca-a7e2-1c57f2315387",
        question:
          "is an icon for the United States Forest Service most famous for the motto 'Give a hootâ€”don't pollute!'",
        options: [
          "Chilly Willy",
          "Cornelius the Rooster",
          "Woodstock",
          "Woodsy Owl",
        ],
        answer: "Woodsy Owl",
      },
      {
        _id: "ae7e36fe-6b6e-4441-9b4c-580c3479fc7d",
        question:
          "_________ often coming to handle Hector the Bulldog or hide behind Granny to avoid the cat, but in the end, he always manages to humiliate Sylvester",
        options: [
          "Tweety Bird",
          "Plucky Duck",
          "Chilly Willy",
          "Yankee Doodle Pigeon",
        ],
        answer: "Tweety Bird",
      },
      {
        _id: "e5480cbc-c6e4-42a0-a2e4-8a85d37a065c",
        question:
          "_________ is a short green duck with black parted hair and the traditional vampire evening wear",
        options: ["Chilly Willy", "Plucky Duck", "Count Duckula", "Wade Duck"],
        answer: "",
      },
    ],
    categoryId: "stvcat001",
    categoryName: "Bird Quiz",
  },
  {
    _id: "6e5c1829-cc3c-4651-a098-083986f6802f",
    title: "Click 'em Birds",
    totalScore: 10,
    mcqs: [
      {
        _id: "da0cd33c-2d4b-4cbe-b40c-0bc494ab188f",
        question: "Why is bird photography a challenge?",
        options: [
          "birds are prey",
          "birds use survival strategies",
          "both answers",
          "none of them",
        ],
        answer: "both answers",
      },
      {
        _id: "9474694f-5c61-44cf-9ea1-4e4f3360e85f",
        question: "What is a bird survival strategy?",
        options: [
          "camouflaged appearance",
          "easy to reach nests",
          "slow accent to flight",
          "none of them",
        ],
        answer: "camouflaged appearance",
      },
      {
        _id: "a8e4c8b3-2362-4c57-a822-dd7286e81543",
        question:
          "What photographing position is less likely to startle your bird subject?",
        options: [
          "standing on the ground",
          "low to the ground",
          "high in the trees",
          "wearing a bird costume",
        ],
        answer: "low to the ground",
      },
      {
        _id: "37b9a1a9-4947-4d59-9242-587dd915ad90",
        question: "Where is a good location to photograph birds?",
        options: [
          "deserted island",
          "uninhabited mountaintop",
          "roadside on the highway",
          "popular beach",
        ],
        answer: "popular beach",
      },
      {
        _id: "84fe2ff9-f0a0-4cc1-a39f-4d9394cafcf8",
        question:
          "What is the favorite camera choice among professional bird photographers?",
        options: ["Cannon", "Nikon", "Both", "None"],
        answer: "Both",
      },
      {
        _id: "8e01c417-4e7b-4f3c-9b0a-7b86b8de69e7",
        question: "What will attract birds to your backyard?",
        options: [
          "birdfeeders filled with seed",
          "birdbaths filled with water",
          "both answers",
          "none of them",
        ],
        answer: "both answers",
      },
      {
        _id: "cf166f54-a805-4d4c-b6c0-e94ecb2e0813",
        question: "Which of the following tip is false in bird photography?",
        options: [
          "Don't obsess about equipment",
          "Tell a story",
          "background doesn't matter",
          "Capture the action",
        ],
        answer: "background doesn't matter",
      },
      {
        _id: "7ef4c119-7f78-4eeb-a318-d3f56099ec4a",
        question: "",
        options: [
          "Anticipate behavior",
          "Approach the bird",
          "Test exposure regularly",
          "Arrive early and stay late",
        ],
        answer: "Approach the bird",
      },
      {
        _id: "4ac10be9-db5f-4df5-ae2b-4467e00d6f30",
        question:
          "Why does bird photography require manual camera controls for high quality pictures?",
        options: [
          "fast moving subjects",
          "poor lighting",
          "both answers",
          "none of them",
        ],
        answer: "both answers",
      },
      {
        _id: "ae957706-d1b3-402c-a42b-e9883d90b176",
        question: "What is important for filming fast-moving subjects?",
        options: [
          "good lighting",
          "wide-angled lens",
          "telephoto lens",
          "frames per second",
        ],
        answer: "frames per second",
      },
    ],
    categoryId: "stvcat002",
    categoryName: "Photography Quiz",
  },
  {
    _id: "2cdab0a1-b76b-49dc-928a-0fb41b2cb0d2",
    title: "Camera Nerd",
    totalScore: 10,
    mcqs: [
      {
        _id: "a1fe53ae-2abf-4f8c-aab8-a34790733ccd",
        question: "What does the lens size number indicate, such as 35 mm?",
        options: [
          "focal length",
          "film roll size",
          "film speed",
          "camera aperture",
        ],
        answer: "focal length",
      },
      {
        _id: "b17b4211-c54d-4b89-b93d-073be5c50ff2",
        question: "What lens has the narrower scope?",
        options: ["35 mm", "70 mm", "250 mm", "400 mm"],
        answer: "400 mm",
      },
      {
        _id: "7d84263b-b344-458b-aa55-65451597b56a",
        question: "What are lenses less than 35 mm used for?",
        options: [
          "capture faraway subjects",
          "capture wider scenes",
          "general photography",
          "landscape photography",
        ],
        answer: "capture wider scenes",
      },
      {
        _id: "a1f443c4-5f64-4b60-95ea-058040d991e5",
        question: "Why may an image be too dark?",
        options: [
          "too little light",
          "just enough light",
          "too much light",
          "none of them",
        ],
        answer: "too little light",
      },
      {
        _id: "68622945-63d6-4bdd-bf0c-99cb4bb7f69f",
        question: "What is aperture?",
        options: [
          "speed of the shutter",
          "film speed",
          "size of camera lens opening",
          "focal length",
        ],
        answer: "size of camera lens opening",
      },
      {
        _id: "ef3a00da-e8df-4f6d-9770-1a972bae0fc0",
        question:
          "If your hands are shaky, what item should you purchase for professional-looking bird photographs?",
        options: ["slow film", "telephoto lens", "macro lens", "tripod"],
        answer: "tripod",
      },
      {
        _id: "720e4085-9b55-46da-8b07-d2e9a7e2c335",
        question: "What is catchlight?",
        options: [
          "reflection of light in a bird's eyes",
          "aperture setting",
          "shutter speed setting",
          "slow film brand",
        ],
        answer: "reflection of light in a bird's eyes",
      },
      {
        _id: "e4a734bb-8277-417d-9623-aacee7b4964c",
        question: "What is the best type of camera for bird shots?",
        options: [
          "digital single lens reflex camera",
          "single lens reflex camera",
          "point-and-shoot camera",
          "none of them",
        ],
        answer: "digital single lens reflex camera",
      },
      {
        _id: "9310ced3-e81d-4c6b-9ad1-ad0aec41d41e",
        question:
          "How is a single lens reflex camera a compatible and adaptable choice?",
        options: [
          "more control over settings",
          "wide variety of lens",
          "both answers",
          "none of them",
        ],
        answer: "both answers",
      },
      {
        _id: "572c66a7-d1d3-498a-adb5-f8d7578ee363",
        question:
          "What camera is a good choice for a photographer with little experience or knowledge?",
        options: [
          "single lens reflex camera",
          "point-and-shoot cameras",
          "digital single lens reflex camera",
          "Phone camera",
        ],
        answer: "point-and-shoot cameras",
      },
    ],
    categoryId: "stvcat002",
    categoryName: "Photography Quiz",
  },
  {
    _id: "419082f3-4ad8-45d3-974c-6c59f5dc923b",
    title: "Photography Nerd",
    totalScore: 10,
    mcqs: [
      {
        _id: "a2e94767-6da5-4edb-bdd9-ce2421a3d21d",
        question:
          "What is the disadvantage of having a high frames per second (FPS) shooting mode on your camera?",
        options: [
          "Less poses to pick from",
          "The photos will be less sharper",
          "Less chance of getting that magic moment",
          "none of them",
        ],
        answer: "The photos will be less sharper",
      },
      {
        _id: "3db6dcb4-b5f6-4714-84ac-88d7397df882",
        question:
          "It is typically better to underexpose your bird and wildlife photos.",
        options: [
          "True",
          "False",
          "Depends on situation",
          "Use just enough exposure",
        ],
        answer: "False",
      },
      {
        _id: "721c5f97-0226-49ad-8826-1b1f8a01ba75",
        question:
          "If you have a hummingbird feeder on average how often should you clean it?",
        options: [
          "Once per month in warm weather",
          "Once every season",
          "Twice per week in warm weather",
          "Every day",
        ],
        answer: "Twice per week in warm weather",
      },
      {
        _id: "31ebaef9-5b5d-458d-b2e6-df39f59d3fef",
        question:
          "If your photo is overexposed, you will not be able to recover the highlights.",
        options: [
          "True",
          "False",
          "Depends on the situation",
          "You can partially recover",
        ],
        answer: "False",
      },
      {
        _id: "e08b5e16-da7c-4927-9ac3-5619fb8f0035",
        question:
          "Back button focus (BBF) helps your camera's focus system operate faster and more accurately.",
        options: [
          "True",
          "False",
          "Depends on the camera",
          "It helps partially",
        ],
        answer: "False",
      },
      {
        _id: "458199c9-df70-4c05-b61c-b120e6a5c0c9",
        question:
          "If you're doing slow shutter speed panning and your lens has only 1 'stabilization' mode (on or off), what should you generally do?",
        options: [
          "Use a shutter speed above 1/125th sec",
          "Turn Image Stabilization to ON",
          "Turn Image Stabilization to Off",
          "None of them",
        ],
        answer: "Turn Image Stabilization to Off",
      },
      {
        _id: "6aee35df-320a-4775-b980-0b2de5384b3e",
        question:
          "Based on these settings, the most likely reason an image of a slow moving bird resulting not sharp is: f/6.3 | 1/2500th | ISO 800",
        options: [
          "Too slow of a shutter speed",
          "There is too much diffraction at f/6.3",
          "The subject might not be in focus",
          "There is not enough depth of field at f/6.3",
        ],
        answer: "The subject might not be in focus",
      },
      {
        _id: "703b1d6d-2250-4692-a04a-b70d5a4c3daf",
        question: "The ISO tells you...",
        options: [
          "How expensive the camera is",
          "How big the camera sensor is",
          "How many exposures you can make",
          "How sensitive the camera sensor is to light",
        ],
        answer: "How sensitive the camera sensor is to light",
      },
      {
        _id: "82d3193e-4d47-4fe4-b831-bd68d0729580",
        question: "What Are the Elements of the Exposure Triangle?",
        options: [
          "Aperture - White Balance - Shutter Speed",
          "Shutter Speed - ISO - Camera Mode",
          "Aperture - ISO - Shutter Speed",
          "ISO - White Balance - Flash Power",
        ],
        answer: "Aperture - ISO - Shutter Speed",
      },
      {
        _id: "fbaecf88-a455-4c5d-976a-f7d41e14b11c",
        question: "What Is Often a Side Effect of Using a Higher ISO Setting?",
        options: [
          "Colour imbalances",
          "Battery drain",
          "Big green pixels",
          "Digital noise",
        ],
        answer: "Digital noise",
      },
    ],
    categoryId: "stvcat002",
    categoryName: "Photography Quiz",
  },
  {
    _id: "8d9855ee-f215-43f2-a9ca-d6e4558b5f04",
    title: "Asian Sanctuaries",
    totalScore: 10,
    mcqs: [
      {
        _id: "b29ce114-b13d-422f-b0a6-5d4344cc9da1",
        question: "How many bird sanctuaries are there in India?",
        options: ["14", "26", "101", "72"],
        answer: "72",
      },
      {
        _id: "88e0b1b6-ca27-4c7f-a76c-0925daaf5850",
        question: "Where is the largest bird sanctuary in India located?",
        options: ["Maharashtra", "Himachal Pradesh", "Gujarat", "Rajasthan"],
        answer: "Rajasthan",
      },
      {
        _id: "b8fd07c3-71b3-4a9f-b301-4d0b3a92e014",
        question: "Which is the oldest bird sanctuary in India?",
        options: [
          "Vedanthangal Bird Sanctuary",
          "Nal Sarovar Bird Sanctuary",
          "Keoladeo National Park",
          "Gulmarg Wildlife Sanctuary",
        ],
        answer: "Vedanthangal Bird Sanctuary",
      },
      {
        _id: "16749501-7aee-43a4-897a-1cea7c7bdb00",
        question:
          "How many species of birds are there in Bharatput bird sanctuary?",
        options: ["215", "56", "680", "360"],
        answer: "360",
      },
      {
        _id: "741a2f5d-4d36-4183-a7e0-aeac386a271d",
        question:
          "Nepal's first official bird sanctuary was declared in which year?",
        options: ["2012", "2022", "1990", "2003"],
        answer: "2022",
      },
      {
        _id: "4b3f5e95-ae62-47a2-bd3a-851ad9c57e23",
        question: "Which is India's largest water bird sanctuary?",
        options: [
          "Nal Sarovar Bird Sanctuary",
          "The Kanwar Lake Bird Sanctuary",
          "Bharatpur Bird Sanctuary",
          "Gulmarg Wildlife Sanctuary",
        ],
        answer: "Nal Sarovar Bird Sanctuary",
      },
      {
        _id: "6d1bf32c-c8ac-4c2b-8e37-590d208b13f9",
        question:
          "Where is the sanctuary named after ornithologist Salim Moizuddin Abdul Ali located?",
        options: ["Kashmir", "Pakistan", "Goa", "Delhi"],
        answer: "Goa",
      },
      {
        _id: "7febaeea-25af-42d4-a164-8556a4328521",
        question: "What is Nawabganj Bird Sanctuary now known as?",
        options: [
          "Chandra Shekhar Azad Bird Sanctuary",
          "Nal Sarovar Bird Sanctuary",
          "Samaspur Bird Sanctuary",
          "Bakhira Bird Sanctuary",
        ],
        answer: "Chandra Shekhar Azad Bird Sanctuary",
      },
      {
        _id: "46541f0a-5a64-4e18-ada2-e344cdf6574e",
        question: "Which bird sanctuary is known as Heaven of birds?",
        options: [
          "Keoladeo National Park",
          "Vedanthangal Bird Sanctuary",
          "Kumarakom Bird Sanctuary",
          "Kaundinya Bird Sanctuary",
        ],
        answer: "Keoladeo National Park",
      },
      {
        _id: "9cc2063b-2951-4520-97bb-18e6bededbf3",
        question:
          "In which season do most migratory birds come to Keoladeo National Park?",
        options: ["Summer", "Monsoon", "Winter", "Spring"],
        answer: "Winter",
      },
    ],
    categoryId: "stvcat003",
    categoryName: "Sanctuary Quiz",
  },
  {
    _id: "d0b89b2e-efda-486f-be73-bcadb5ab0e6b",
    title: "African Sanctuaries",
    totalScore: 10,
    mcqs: [
      {
        _id: "c1402d28-db28-4a02-8675-879d766767de",
        question:
          "What is the largest free flight bird sanctuary in the world?",
        options: [
          "Serengeti National Park",
          "Birds of Eden",
          "Kruger National Park",
          "Ras al-khor",
        ],
        answer: "Birds of Eden",
      },
      {
        _id: "4676e9db-06b0-4a98-93f6-83142eb2cdb7",
        question:
          "How many sanctuaries are under The South African Animal Sanctuary Alliance (SAASA)?",
        options: ["7", "3", "4", "12"],
        answer: "4",
      },
      {
        _id: "024e2389-01d2-4cc9-b4d7-f73c6ef238c7",
        question: "Roughly how many birds are there in Birds of Eden?",
        options: ["1000", "50000", "2500", "3500"],
        answer: "3500",
      },
      {
        _id: "e75d8b3d-9f23-4c1f-87e0-9aa7b864712e",
        question: "How many wildlife sanctuaries are there in Africa?",
        options: ["10", "67", "15", "103"],
        answer: "15",
      },
      {
        _id: "c2d40601-efdf-4947-b4a1-9de8ccd5d133",
        question: "Which is South Africa's largest wildlife sanctuary?",
        options: [
          "Kruger National Park",
          "Serengeti National Park",
          "Amboseli National Park",
          "Chobe National Park",
        ],
        answer: "Kruger National Park",
      },
      {
        _id: "46e953a5-aa82-4121-8ff5-e5501b48ced2",
        question: "Where is Masai Mara National Park located?",
        options: ["Tanzania", "Kenya", "South Africa", "Zimbabwe"],
        answer: "Kenya",
      },
      {
        _id: "a15cf882-0524-417b-8027-d521517a5ec4",
        question:
          "Which is the only place in Africa where vast land-animal migrations still take place?",
        options: [
          "Serengeti National Park",
          "Amboseli National Park",
          "Chobe National Park",
          "Etosha National Park",
        ],
        answer: "Serengeti National Park",
      },
      {
        _id: "7cb0037c-7593-426d-b6cb-ce664bee66d4",
        question:
          "Which sanctuary in Tanzania is the world's largest inactive, unbroken and unfilled volcanic caldera?",
        options: [
          "Moremi Game Reserve",
          "Serengeti National Park",
          "Maasai Mara National Reserve",
          "Ngorongoro Conservation Area",
        ],
        answer: "Ngorongoro Conservation Area",
      },
      {
        _id: "7dd6a1d5-a34a-410f-a21d-9f7c42d04e3c",
        question:
          "Which national park in southern Kenya has the highest peak on the African continent?",
        options: [
          "Amboseli National Park",
          "Maasai Mara National Reserve",
          "Kruger National Park",
          "Chobe National Park",
        ],
        answer: "Amboseli National Park",
      },
      {
        _id: "afa1b0db-6aac-4395-bd39-b9d317712e41",
        question:
          "Which national park in Botswana is famous for its massive elephant populations and incredible birdlife?",
        options: [
          "Moremi Game Reserve",
          "Etosha National Park",
          "Chobe National Park",
          "Amboseli National Park",
        ],
        answer: "Chobe National Park",
      },
    ],
    categoryId: "stvcat003",
    categoryName: "Sanctuary Quiz",
  },
];
